Guide to the Marilyn Skolnick Papers, 1952-2009 AIS.2001.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio-Visual Material, 1987-2009; VII.
  - Audio Cassettes, 1994-1996; 2.
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: "Where Do We Go From Here?,"" Tape 2, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 28)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: "Where Do We Go From Here?,"" Tape 3, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 29)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: Conference Results," Tape 1, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 30)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: Conference Results," Tape 2, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 31)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Public Involvement and ISTEA: Conference Results," Tape 3, January 1994 (Box 73, Item 32)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Major Investment Studies: Issues in a Multimodal Process," Tape 1, January 1995 (Box 73, Item 33)
    - Transportation Research Board, "Major Investment Studies: Issues in a Multimodal Process," Tape 2, January 1995 (Box 73, Item 34)
    - Habsfrau, September 27-28, 1996 (Box 73, Item 35)
    - Sludge and incineration, undated (Box 73, Item 36)
    - Untitled microcassette, undated (Box 73, Item 37)
    - Untitled microcassette, undated (Box 73, Item 38)